If you wanted to drill to the bottom of
Antarctica, the first thing you need to
realize is this ice is way thicker than
you think. If we were to take a chunk
out of this ice and place it on the
surface, at its thickest, it would be
this tall.
Wow, that's nearly the height of Mount
Kilimanjaro. You would have to stack the
tallest building in the world six times
to reach the top of that.
And this isn't just one uniform block.
It's full of all different kinds of ice.
And if you looked into the hole left
behind by our chunk, you'd see
land.
>> That is totally different than the North
Pole. It turns out there's a lot more
going on under Antarctica than we ever
thought. To see it, subscribe.